http://www.illinoistollway.com/privacy-information

Construction and Engineering Overview
Bids and Bulletins (PSBs)
PREAMBLE
Pursuant to the fundamental philosophy of the American constitutional form of government, it is declared to be the public policy of the State of Illinois that all persons are entitled to full and complete information regarding the affairs of government and the official acts and policies of those who represent them as public officials and public employees. The access to this information is not intended to be used to violate individual privacy, nor to further a commercial enterprise, nor to disrupt the duly-undertaken work of any public body independent of the fulfillment of any of rights of the people to access to information.
PERSONAL INFORMATION AND CHOICE
"Personal information" is information about an individual that is readily identifiable to that specific individual. Personal information includes personal identifiers such as an individual's name, address, phone number, drivers license number and social security number. A domain name or Internet Protocol address is not considered personal information. We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily participate in an activity that asks for information (e.g., sending an email, setting up an I-PASS account or participating in a survey). If you choose not to participate in these activities, your choice will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature of the Illinois Tollway Web site. If personal information is requested on the web site or volunteered by the user, State law and the federal Privacy Act of 1974 may protect it. However, this information is a public record once you provide it, and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not protected by federal or state law.
WEB LOGS
The Illinois Tollway analyzes our website logs to continually improve the value of the materials available on our site. Our website logs are not personally identifiable. When a visitor requests a page from any of our Web sites, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Sites. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate and we do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record email addresses of the visitors.
CORRESPONDENCE
If during your visit to the Illinois Tollway website you participate in a survey or send an email, the following additional information will be collected: 1. Email correspondence: The email address and contents of the email. We may use your email to respond appropriately. This may be to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to further improve our Web site, or to forward the email to another agency for appropriate action. 2. Surveys : Any information you volunteered in response to a survey. Survey information is used for the purpose designated. The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats that you have provided.
COOKIES
A "cookie" is a small file containing information that is placed on a user's computer by a Web server. Typically, these files are used to enhance the user's experience of the site, to help users move between pages in a database, or to customize information for a user. Several Illinois Tollway Web pages are set up to use "cookies" to enhance a user's experience with the agency's site. Cookies are text files placed on a user's computer to store preferences and session information only. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system.
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.
Our  Web usage analysis software uses cookies in order to provide meaningful reports about site visitors' activities and usage, but these cookies do not collect personal data about any  website visitor.
DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY
Neither the State of Illinois nor any of its employees shall be held liable for any improper or incorrect use of the information described and/or contained herein and assumes no responsibility for anyone's use of the information. In no event shall the State website or its employees be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages (including, but not limited to, procurement or substitute goods or services; loss of use, data, or profits; or business interruption) however caused and on any theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability, or tort (including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of the use of this system, even if advised of the possibility of such damage. This disclaimer of liability applies to any damages or injury, including but not limited to those caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use of record, whether for breach of contract, tortuous behavior, negligence or under any other cause of action.
DISCLAIMER OF ENDORSEMENT
The Illinois State Toll Highway Authority is a distributor of content sometimes supplied by third parties and users. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers, or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties, including information providers, users, or others, are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and do not necessarily state or reflect those of the State of Illinois and shall not be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes. Reference herein to any specific commercial products, process, or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, or otherwise, does not constitute or imply its endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the State.
DISCLAIMER OF DUTY TO CONTINUE PROVISION OF DATA
Due to the dynamic nature of the Internet, resources that are free and publicly available one day may require a fee or restricted access the next, and the location of items may change as menus, home pages, and files are reorganized. The user expressly agrees that use of the Authority's website is at the user's sole risk. The Authority does not warrant that the service will be uninterrupted or error free. The documents and related graphics published on this server could contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically added to the information herein. The State and/or its respective agencies and programs may make improvements and/or changes in the information and/or programs described herein at any time.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Information collected and received through the Illinois Tollway Web site may become public record and therefore subject to disclosure under the Illinois Freedom of Information Act. It is therefore the policy of the Illinois Tollway that no personal information you provide to us, including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, drivers license number, Social Security Number and email address will be sold or rented to any entity or individual or disclose to any unauthorized entity or individual.
The release of personal information by the Departments under the control of the Governor shall be limited, according to Illinois law, to the State of Illinois government agencies and/or to authorized Department contractors or grantees.
POLICIES FOR INDIVIDUALS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE
The Illinois Tollway is committed to complying fully with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Accordingly, if you are under the age of 13, you are not authorized to provide us with personally identifying information, and we will not use any such information in our database or other data collection activities. We appreciate your cooperation with this federally mandated requirement. Users are cautioned that the collection of personal information volunteered by children on-line or by email will be treated the same as information given by an adult and may be subject to public access.
INFORMATION RETAINED AND HOW IT IS USED
During your visit to the Illinois State Tollway's website, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:
The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website.
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site.
The date and time you access our site.
The pages you visit.
If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.
We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.
LINK DISCLAIMER
The Illinois State Toll Highway Authority has links to other websites. These include links to web sites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations and private businesses. When you link to another site, you are no longer on a site covered by this Privacy Notice. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. Please see the information below for a complete list of those URLs that are covered by this privacy policy.
LEGAL NOTICES
Access to the Illinois State Toll Highway Authority web site is provided subject to the following terms and conditions. Please read these terms carefully as use of these sites constitutes acceptance of all of the following terms and conditions:
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND ACCURACY OF DATA
Although the data found using the Illinois State Toll Highway Authority access systems have been produced and processed from sources believed to be reliable, no warranty, expressed or implied, is made regarding accuracy, adequacy, completeness, legality, reliability or usefulness of any information. This disclaimer applies to both isolated and aggregate uses of the information. The State provides this information on an "as is" basis. All warranties of any kind, express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, freedom from contamination by computer viruses and non-infringement of proprietary rights are disclaimed. Changes may be periodically made to the information herein; these changes may or may not be incorporated in any new version of the publication. If you have obtained information from any of the Illinois State Toll Highway Authority's web pages from a source other than the Authority's web pages, be aware that electronic data can be altered subsequent to original distribution. Data can also quickly become out of date. It is recommended that careful attention be paid to the contents of any data associated with a file, and that the originator of the data or information be contacted with any questions regarding appropriate use. If you find any errors or omissions, we encourage you to report them using the Authority's web page email link.
DISCLAIMER OF EXTERNAL LINKS
The Illinois State Toll Highway Authority's website contains links to other related World Wide Web Internet sites and resources. The Authority is not responsible for the contents of any off-site pages referenced. The user specifically acknowledges that the Authority is not liable for the defamatory, offensive, or illegal conduct of other users, links, or third parties and that the risk of injury from the foregoing rests entirely with the user. Links from the Authority's web pages on the World Wide Web to other sites do not constitute an endorsement from the State. These links are provided as an information service only. It is the responsibility of the web surfer to evaluate the content and usefulness of information obtained from other sites. Since the Illinois State Toll Highway Authority's website is not responsible for the availability of these outside resources or their contents, you should direct any concerns regarding any external link to its site administrator or webmaster.
CHOICE OF LAW
Construction of the disclaimers above and resolution of disputes thereof are governed by the laws of the State of Illinois. The laws of the State of Illinois, U.S.A., shall apply to all uses of this data and this system. By use of this system and any data contained therein, the user agrees that use shall conform to all applicable laws and regulations and user shall not violate the rights of any third parties.
Top
×
Tweets by @I_90_Tollway
Follow @I_90_Tollway
Tweets by @94_294_Tollway
Follow @I_90_Tollway
Tweets by @I_88_Tollway
Follow @I_90_Tollway
